just don't understand why Amanda seals
is just always in victim mode like I I
really feel like she's just one of those
Hollywood kids and I just feel like
she's just feels like she's entitled you
know people have to do this for me they
have to back me up I just don't
understand like why you out here pulling
a Monique on isay like isay has to go
through different barriers that you've
gone through because you simply have
been grandfathered in why are you why
you out here talking about what somebody
did to me why they won't let me in rooms
and I'm be honest with you I've spoken
to several high-profile figures that are
in Hollywood that are doing the invites
she gets invited to all of them and you
know what she does and this listen this
is according to them and according to
Amanda because she said that she was on
the Spectrum high functioning Spectrum
okay now they say every time she gets
the invite she goes in the corner and
don't talk to
nobody they stop inviting her